cloudhashing.com 2014-10-10

# Privacy - Cloud Hashing - Bitcoin Mining Contracts

At CloudHashing we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. 

This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site. 

### Scope of this Policy

The CloudHashing Privacy Policy applies to Technology IQ Ltd (a company incorporated in England and Wales with number 0841855) with registered office at 145-147 St. John Street, London, EC1V 4PW (" **CloudHashing** " or “ **we** ”). This Privacy Policy Statement explains how CloudHashing uses personal information collected or processed in connection with the provision of the CloudHashing service (the “ **Service** ”). 

The Service is a Bitcoin mining service. The individual or organisation that registers for Our Service will be referred to as the “ **Subscriber** ” or “ **you** ”.

### "Personal Information"

The CloudHashing Privacy Policy concerns the use by CloudHashing of personal Information. Personal Information, or “personally identifiable information”, as it is sometimes known, is generally a reference to data that can be linked to or identified with a living individual.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any data insofar as it is held, processed, disclosed or published in a form which cannot be linked to a living individual (such as anonymised data, aggregated data, or coded data which, in a given form, cannot effectively be used to extract Personal Information) (" **Generic Data** "). CloudHashing reserves the right to generate Generic Data out of any databases containing Personal Information and to make such use as it sees fit of any such Generic Data.

### Who processes Personal Information?

This Privacy Policy concerns Personal Information processed by or for CloudHashing.

Where Personal Information is collected from you in connection with your use of the Service or where CloudHashing obtains your consent to the use of your Personal Information, CloudHashing is responsible for the processing and storing of such Personal Information.

### Personal Information collected in connection with the distribution of products, services and software

In order to provide the Service, CloudHashing requires Subscribers to provide minimal details namely a username and email address when they register to the Service. CloudHashing uses Personal Information provided by Subscribers for the purpose of communicating with the Subscriber and administering, delivering and improving the Service.

CloudHashing may also use such data (insofar as permitted under applicable law) to communicate with you in relation to other products or services offered by CloudHashing or its partners. In accordance with the requirements of applicable law, CloudHashing may request you to confirm your consent for such communications ('opt-in') or to indicate that you would not like to receive such communications, or that such communication should be discontinued ('opt-out').

Where you give an opt-out notice, CloudHashing will not use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes (but this shall not prevent use of the Personal Information in relation to the administration of the Service, or to provide technical and other support to you in relation to the Service).

Where an opt-in is required by applicable law as a pre-requisite for sending direct marketing communications, CloudHashing will not use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes unless you provide the requisite opt-in. 

CloudHashing does not share Personal Information obtained from its Subscribers with any third parties (other than partners of CloudHashing in connection with the Service or as further explained in this Privacy Policy) except where you have given your consent or to assist you to share your Personal Information with other Subscribers.

### Other forms in which Personal Information may be used

We may disclose Personal Information to third parties if we believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply the Terms of Use or Terms or Conditions of Supply that a Subscriber accepted in relation to the Service or to the use of our website or in order to protect the rights, property, safety and integrity of CloudHashing or the Service, or otherwise as provided by law or required by any court of competent jurisdiction or any regulatory authority acting under statutory powers.

There may be limited circumstances in which CloudHashing may be required to disclose Personal Information to unrelated third parties: 

  * There may be times when Personal Information must be disclosed in response to the following: (1) where necessary to satisfy a legitimate government request or direction or in response to a court order including for law enforcement, investigation and national security purposes or in connection with legal proceedings; (2) in response to a third-party subpoena, if on legal advice such response is required; or (3) if necessary to defend CloudHashing, or its partners or other Subscribers (for example, in a lawsuit). 
  * If you request a specific service or product, and if that product or service is administered by a third party who is working for or in partnership with CloudHashing, your Personal Information may be shared with the third party in order to respond to the request. The third party in question may also transmit back to CloudHashing any new information obtained from you or about you in connection with providing the service or product.

CloudHashing will fully co-operate with law enforcement, investigation and security agencies and regulators to identify anyone who uses its service or software for illegal activities. CloudHashing reserves the right to report to law enforcement, investigation and security agencies and to regulators any activities that are believed to be unlawful.

As explained elsewhere in this CloudHashing Privacy Policy, Personal Information collected by CloudHashing may be processed by CloudHashing partners in providing related services to CloudHashing (such as such as administration services, technical services relating to the maintenance, servicing and upgrading of the products, software or services provided by CloudHashing, hosting services, data migration services and analytical services, among others). CloudHashing ensures that such partners or service providers do not use any such Personal Information for any other purposes, that they do not disclose it to any third parties and that they do not retain copies of such data except as necessary to provide services to CloudHashing or its customers or as may be required by law.

### Other third parties that may have access to Personal Information

We reserve the right to disclose and transfer Personal Information to other entities in connection with the sale or transfer of our business or those business activities relating to the products or service in connection with which the Personal Information has been collected (including, where necessary, in negotiations towards such sale or transfer). We will ensure that such acquirer will continue to process the Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (as it may be updated from time to time).

### Storage, security and retention of Personal Information

Personal Information that CloudHashing collects is stored on its servers (which may be located outside the EEA). We implement and maintain adequate security measures to protect such information stored on our servers and seek to comply with all local rules in respect of storage of data. CloudHashing also strives to collect no more Personal Information from Subscribers than is required for the purpose for which it is collected. This, in turn, helps reduce the total risk of harm should data loss or a breach in security occur.

Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. Whilst we shall use reasonable efforts to protect the security of Personal Information about you, we cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically. Sending such information is entirely at your own risk.

### Notification in the event of breach

In the unlikely event of a breach in the security of Personal Information, CloudHashing may decide to notify any Subscriber who is actually or potentially affected. CloudHashing may elect to give notice via in-product messaging systems or via email (if such data is available to CloudHashing). Notice of data breach may also be given via publication on company website or on the product portals. Subject to applicable legal and regulatory requirements, CloudHashing reserves the right to decide whether or not to give notice of a data breach to Subscribers, and which Subscribers should be notified, and reserves the right to delay notification if it is asked to do so by law enforcement or other authorities, or if CloudHashing believes that giving notice will increase the risk of harm to its Subscribers.

### "Sensitive" information

CloudHashing does not collect "sensitive" Personal Information such as sexual preference, religion, political views, or health. CloudHashing does not wish to receive any such data and will not request it.

### Data on children

Persons under the age of 18 should not transfer personal information to us unless they have the consent of their parent(s) or guardian(s). We do not knowingly collect, nor do we want to receive, personal information about individuals who are under 16 years of age.

### Third Party Links

On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.

### Use of Cookies

Please see our website Cookie Policy page for more information on use of cookies.

### Access to Information

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a fee of £10 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information. 

### Contacting CloudHashing about privacy questions or concerns

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or any queries, requests or complaints in regard to the Service or the use of your Personal Information, please contact CloudHashing by sending an email to the following address (indicating "PRIVACY REQUEST" in the message line): support@cloudhashing.com.

or by sending a letter to: Technology IQ LTD 145-147 St. John Street, London, EC1V 4PW

If you contact CloudHashing by e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. We may ask for your name, e-mail address and contact information in order to send you a reply.

### Changes to your Personal Information and unsubscribing from the Service

You may change or request that we delete the Personal Information that CloudHashing retains about you by contacting us either via email or by sending a letter.

We will permanently and irretrievably delete all Personal Information we hold on your behalf following your instructions to do so, save that: 

  1. copies of your Personal Information may remain stored for limited periods of time on back-up media which shall be cleansed from time to time;
  2. CloudHashing reserves the right to retain records of your Personal Information if we reasonably require to maintain such records for legal purposes including to comply with our legal or regulatory duties, to investigate and respond to complaints (including from other Subscribers), to enforce our Terms of Use or to defend ourselves against any claim or legal threat or allegations, or if we require to retain such data for other legitimate reasons; and
  3. CloudHashing shall be entitled to retain any data in non-Personal Information form which may have been extracted or obtained from your Personal Information including any aggregated, anonymised or otherwise de-personalised data.

### Privacy Policy changes

This Privacy Policy was last changed on 2014-1-08. If CloudHashing makes changes to the Privacy Policy, the new version will be posted on the Service. CloudHashing may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless stated otherwise.
